Password Reset Confirmation
---------------------------

If an account matching the email you entered was found, you will receive an email with a link to reset your password.

User Not Found
--------------

The username/email and password combination you entered was not found. Please try again or contact support.

Enable Dark Mode

* Quizzes & Apps
    
    [World's Smallest Political Quiz
    
    Where do you stand politically?
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/quiz/)
    
    [Human Respect Tests
    
    Do you endorse political coercion?
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/human-respect-tests/)
    
    [Political Surveys
    
    Survey and compare your beliefs
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/single-issue-surveys/)
    
    [Compare Political Types
    
    Learn About The Nolan Chart
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/political-type-comparison/)
    
    Most Popular
    
    * [

        ### The World’s Smallest Political Quiz
        
        Discover your political type and what your answers mean
        
        Read more
        
        23242153 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        2.5 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/the-worlds-smallest-political-quiz/)
        
    * [

        ### Gun Control Survey
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        850 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        7 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/gun-control-survey/)
        
    * [

        ### Federal Spending Survey
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        2270 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        4.5 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/federal-spending-survey/)
        
    * [

        ### National Security And Foreign Policy
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        2500 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        4 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/national-security-survey/)
        
    * [

        ### Government Debt, Money, and Monetary Policy
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        1140 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/government-debt-money-and-monetary-policy/)
        
    * [

        ### Identity Politics and Political Correctness
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        2250 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        4 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/identity-politics-and-political-correctness/)
        
    * [

        ### Censorship and Free Speech
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        1950 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        4.5 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/censorship-and-free-speech/)
        
    * [

        ### Election Integrity Survey
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        860 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/election-integrity-survey/)
        
    * [

        ### Pandemic Survey
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        1450 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        4 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/pandemic-survey/)
        
    * [

        ### Police Accountability
        
        Discover if your political type score matches with your views on specific issues, and compare your results to others.
        
        Read more
        
        1120 Respondents  
        by **The Advocates**
        
        Duration
        
        3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/police-accountability/)

* Political Types
    
    [Libertarian
    
    What it Means to be a Libertarian
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/libertarian/)
    
    [Conservative
    
    What it Means to be a Conservative
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/conservative/)
    
    [Progressive
    
    What it Means to be a Progressive
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/liberal/)
    
    [Moderate
    
    What it Means to be a Moderate
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/moderate/)
    
    [Authoritarian
    
    What it Means to be a Authoritarian
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/authoritarian/)
    
    Political Types
    
    * [

        Libertarian
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/libertarian/)
        
    * [

        Conservative
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/conservative/)
        
    * [

        Progressive
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/liberal/)
        
    * [

        Moderate
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/moderate/)
        
    * [

        Authoritarian
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/authoritarian/)

* Articles
    
    [All Articles
    
    See All Articles
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/articles/)
    
    [Underthrow Series
    
    See Underthrow Series Articles
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/category/underthrow-series/)
    
    [Video & Film
    
    See Video & Film Articles
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/category/asg-stream/)
    
    [Education
    
    See Education Articles
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/category/education/)
    
    Latest Articles
    
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        We Have to Clean Up the Mess Ourselves
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/we-have-to-clean-up-the-mess-ourselves/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        In the Ashes of the Apparatus
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/in-the-ashes-of-the-apparatus/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        Bug Bites and Bureaucrats
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/bug-bites-and-bureaucrats/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        Old Man Mountain Weeps
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/old-man-mountain-weeps/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        The A Word (Gasp) – Anarchy
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/the-a-word-gasp-anarchy/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        Makers and Takers
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/makers-and-takers/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        Blinking Lights: Heroes of Underthrow
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/blinking-lights-heroes-of-underthrow/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        Anything Peaceful
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/anything-peaceful/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        What’s So Great About Polycentricity?
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/whats-so-great-about-polycentricity/)
        
    *   [

        Underthrow Series
        
        When Governments Compete, You Win
        
        by **Max Borders**
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/when-governments-compete-you-win/)

    [Our Mission
    
    Who We Are
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/about/)
    
    [Donate
    
    Make a donation
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/donate/)
    
    [Be A Patron
    
    Select Membership level
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/membership/)
    
    [Shop
    
    Source for libertarian books
    
    Read more](https://shop.www.theadvocates.org/)
    
    More Links
    
    *   [

        Our Mission
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/libertarian/)
        
    *   [

        Donate
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/donate/)
        
    *   [

        Be A Patron
        
        Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/liberal/)
        
    *   [

        Shop
        
        Read more](https://shop.www.theadvocates.org/)

Enable Dark Mode

Quizzes & Apps
--------------

*   [

    ### Freedom of Speech & Expression
    
    You'll be given 3 possible answers per question.
    
    Read more
    
    Human Respect Tests

    by **ASG Author**
    
    Duration
    
    3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/freedom-of-speech-and-expression/)
    
*   [

    ### Freedom of Association
    
    You'll be given 3 possible answers per question.
    
    Read more
    
    Human Respect Tests

    by **ASG Author**
    
    Duration
    
    3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/freedom-of-association/)
    
*   [

    ### Freedom of Privacy
    
    You'll be given 3 possible answers per question.
    
    Read more
    
    Human Respect Tests

    by **ASG Author**
    
    Duration
    
    3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/freedom-of-privacy/)
    
*   [

    ### Education Freedom Respect
    
    You'll be given 3 possible answers per question.
    
    Read more
    
    Human Respect Tests

    by **ASG Author**
    
    Duration
    
    3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/education-freedom/)
    
*   [

    ### Healthcare Respect
    
    You'll be given 3 possible answers per question.
    
    Read more
    
    Human Respect Tests

    by **ASG Author**
    
    Duration
    
    3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/freedom-of-bodily-autonomy-copy-copy/)
    
*   [

    ### Personal Choice & Victimless Crimes
    
    You'll be given 3 possible answers per question.
    
    Read more
    
    Human Respect Tests

    by **ASG Author**
    
    Duration
    
    3 Min](https://www.theadvocates.org/qep/personal-choice-victimless-crimes/)

Articles
--------

*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    We Have to Clean Up the Mess Ourselves
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/we-have-to-clean-up-the-mess-ourselves/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    In the Ashes of the Apparatus
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/in-the-ashes-of-the-apparatus/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    Bug Bites and Bureaucrats
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/bug-bites-and-bureaucrats/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    Old Man Mountain Weeps
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/old-man-mountain-weeps/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    The A Word (Gasp) – Anarchy
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/the-a-word-gasp-anarchy/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    Makers and Takers
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/makers-and-takers/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    Blinking Lights: Heroes of Underthrow
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/blinking-lights-heroes-of-underthrow/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    Anything Peaceful
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/anything-peaceful/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    What’s So Great About Polycentricity?
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/whats-so-great-about-polycentricity/)
    
*   [

    Underthrow Series
    
    When Governments Compete, You Win
    
    by **Max Borders**
    
    Read more](https://www.theadvocates.org/when-governments-compete-you-win/)

### Privacy Policy

The Advocates for Self-Government (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://theadvocatesp.kinsta.cloud website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

Information Collection And Use
------------------------------

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address, other information (“Personal Information”).

We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services.

### Log Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service’s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

### Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

### Behavioral Remarketing

The Advocates for Self-Government uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

### Google

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: https://www.google.com/settings/ads

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

Our Service utilizes Google’s Invisible reCAPTCHA to validate human users for some or all of the user input forms available on the Service.

### Facebook

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/#568137493302217

Facebook adheres the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA https://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada https://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation

### Do Not Track Disclosure

We support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

Compliance With Laws
--------------------

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

Security
--------

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

International Transfer
----------------------

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Links To Other Sites
--------------------

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy
------------------

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Changes To This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 23, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@theadvocates.org with the subject heading “Privacy Policy.”

New Here?

Already have your results? [Log in.](#loginbox)

### Start My Political Identity Journey

### What Are The 5 Political Types

The Advocates

Political Types

Quizzes & Surveys

Your Account

©2011-2024 The Advocates | [Terms & Conditions](https://www.theadvocates.org/terms-conditions/) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.theadvocates.org/privacy-policy/)

#### Sign Up with Email

Save your results & progress. It’s Free, forever.

Don't have an account yet? [Create one!](#)

Click “Sign Up” to agree to The Advocate’s For Self Governments’ [Terms of Service](https://www.www.theadvocates.org/terms-conditions/) and acknowledge that The Advocate’s [Privacy Policy](https://www.www.theadvocates.org/privacy-policy/) applies to you. You also consent to receive our email newsletter which you can opt out of at any time.

#### Join free or login to save results.

Save your results & progress. It’s free, forever.

Already have an account? [Login](#)

Click “Sign Up” to agree to The Advocate’s For Self Governments’ [Terms of Service](https://www.www.theadvocates.org/terms-conditions/) and acknowledge that The Advocate’s [Privacy Policy](https://www.www.theadvocates.org/privacy-policy/) applies to you. You also consent to receive our email newsletter which you can opt out of at any time.

#### Sign in with email.

Username or Email Address 

Password 

 Remember Me

#### Sign up with email.

Sign up for our newsletter 

Note: Your password will be generated automatically and emailed to the email address you specify above.

[

My Journey](https://www.theadvocates.org/)
